{
    "subject": "resource/Requeij\u00e3o",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Requeij\u00e3o",
    "human_readable": "Requeij\u00e3o is primarily about Requeij\u00e3o.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9827709794044495,
            "question": "What is Requeij\u00e3o primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773258328437805,
            "question": "Is there a specific topic or concept that Requeij\u00e3o focuses on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8255249261856079,
            "question": "Can you describe the main subject matter of Requeij\u00e3o?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8073185682296753,
            "question": "How does Requeij\u00e3o approach the subject matter of Requeij\u00e3o?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7952080965042114,
            "question": "Based on its name, what can you infer about the potential content of Requeij\u00e3o?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947477698326111,
            "question": "Is there a particular perspective or viewpoint presented in Requeij\u00e3o regarding its primary focus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620499730110168,
            "question": "What kind of information does Requeij\u00e3o provide about its central topic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7340973019599915,
            "question": "Does Requeij\u00e3o delve into any specific aspects or details related to its main subject?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7181280255317688,
            "question": "What is the central theme explored in Requeij\u00e3o?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7071655988693237,
            "question": "What is the overall purpose or goal of Requeij\u00e3o in relation to its central topic?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Requeij\u00e3o is primarily about Requeij\u00e3o.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1593_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the central theme explored in Requeij\u00e3o?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1593_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Requeij\u00e3o delve into any specific aspects or details related to its main subject?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1593_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of information does Requeij\u00e3o provide about its central topic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1593_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1593_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nRequeij\u00e3o is the main subject of all the provided documents.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about requeij\u00e3o and its variations, confirming that the text is primarily about requeij\u00e3o."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}